kdice.com 2019-07-20

# 

This privacy policy sets out how KDice, Gpokr, and XSketch uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website. KDice, Gpokr, and XSketch are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. KDice, Gpokr, and XSketch may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 14th of April, 2012. 

**What we collect**  
We optionally collect the following information: 

  * name
  * contact information including email address

You can optionally decide to provide the following information: 

  * demographic information such as city, country, sex, and birthday

**What we do with the information we gather**  
We use this information to build your public profile so that you can share with other visitors. We do use this information for promotional purposes. We may use your contact information to assist you with the service or to inform you about updates. 

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How we use cookies**  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes. 

**Controlling your personal information**   
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * go to your profile settings and remove your personal information
  * email us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) requesting personal information to be removed

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information.
